dr. O'Connor what are the benefits of
anavar so innovar was the first oral
antibiotic steroid that was produced in
the 1960s the concept was to make an
oral antibiotic steroid that is more
anabolic in the Sandro genic and
androgyny City refers to the male
secondary sex characteristics obviously
that make men men and would that become
various side effects from hair loss acne
mood changes and so on and so forth so
to have a substance that's more anabolic
actually than testosterone much more
anabolic unless androgenic would have
been a great idea and indeed this is why
this is one of the first drugs oral
drugs that was produced at that time for
that purpose why was the inner fire
taking off the market so anavar came
into the market in the mid 1960s in
America and also in Europe and through
the 60s into the 70s and into the mid in
late 80s it was used more and more some
medically and it was obviously widely
abused performance-enhancing drug like
and it was used by athletes and also
starting to be used during that time
period for even just personal use
including women just for fitness and
personal aesthetic reasons widely abused
though across the board by Track & Field
widely abused by NFL during the 70s and
into the 80s and always widely abused by
bodybuilders and it came to July 1st
1989 and it was legally removed for the
market in America at that time
how much does anavar cost so very
interesting that's always a popular
question because anavar is very
expensive and the reason why it's
thought to be expensive is because the
raw ingredients are more difficult to
make than other drugs like when straw
for an example and die in a ball so you
could pay in the black market this
is only black market of course and this
film was strictly for educational
purposes of course this you could pay up
to over $2 per pill for legitimate
anavar and other medicines are going to
be a fraction maybe a quarter or even
1/10 of that price what can go wrong
when by an anavar on the black market so
any medication that anyone's buying this
day and age on the black market off the
internet for an example or from someone
you don't know that's not a physician
you can get the medicine can be
contaminated the medicine quality
control is always going to be concerning
and you may not actually be getting
medicine we see all the time in America
with legitimate medicines where you
think you're getting a anti cholesterol
or hypertensive medicine but you're
actually getting a anti-diabetic or a
diabetic medication so this is going to
be huge severe consequences so it's very
dangerous and highly advised not to do
this thank you thank you